Alex Coldicott
6 West View
Hull
HU5 2UZ
07938720570
alex.coldicott@outlook.com

Profile:

I am a highly motivated and attentive individual that is constantly looking to improve my ability to work effectively. Working in teams is something I enjoy however I also enjoy working alone and I am more than happy to take on tasks that are outside of my comfort zone. Being an experienced team leader, I am comfortable taking the lead if required, however, This does not impair my respect for the chain of command. I have studied a range of courses over several years and have gained a lot of experience from a diversity of employment as well. I feel this has given me the skills and self-awareness needed to be as productive as possible and align my goals within the requirements of my role.

Employment:

Complaints Manager, Clear Answer, hull, East riding of Yorkshire

April 2019 - July 2019

Investigate complaints and liaise with other departments within the company in order to understand where issues have occurred. Calculate, negotiate and justify compensation. Hand in end of day and end of week reports. Use a variety of internal systems to achieve my gaols. Work towards targets.

Crew member, McDonalds, hull, East riding of Yorkshire

September 2018 - April 2019

Cooking and preparing food quickly, presenting food to a high standard, deep cleaning and maintaining high standards of hygiene, serving customers and preparing orders quickly with good presentation.

Sales agent, ResQ, Hull, East Riding of Yorkshire

May 2017 - June 2018

Researching and understanding telecommunication products and services. Pitching the appropriate products and services based on customer needs. Keeping up to date with changes within the industry Building a call structure that is concise and engaging.

Focusing heavily on building rapport as quickly as possible with customers. Working towards individual and team targets

Daine and the second and the second

Being positive and energetic on every call.

Team Member, The Tower Tavern, Mablethorpe, Lincolnshire

June 2016 - November 2016

Maintaining high hygiene standards behind the bar and in customer areas. Building rapport with customers was vital as the bar is located on a holiday site with many long term visitors. General duties included and were not limited to changing barrels and other stock control, using tills and cleaning.

Assistant Manager, The Duke of York (Batemans), Boston, Lincolnshire

September 2014 – January 2016

Using excellent customer service at all times while maintaining the standards of many aspects of the establishment. My main duties included delegating work, managing the kitchen area and behind the bar, ordering and maintaining stock, general till duties and cleaning, business to business networking, advertising and event planning, and overall, helping to create a fantastic atmosphere for my customers.

Supervisor, Spar, Bourne Leisure, Mablethorpe, Lincolnshire

April 2011 – November 2013

Working on a busy holiday site, I gained lots of experience in a range of departments such as reception, check in, touring, arcade and catering. My general duties were in store and included using tills and managing stock, safe checks, delegating work, ordering and managing frozen stock, merchandising and warehouse management.

Assistant, Mambo Wheels, Manby, Lincolnshire

July 2009 – November 2009

I was a general assistant in a small alloy refurbishment business and my duties included using heavy duty machinery and air compression tools to prepare alloys for refurbishment and refitting.

Voluntary work:

7Cups.com - I volunteered for about one year to speak to people online with anxiety, depression and addiction issues.

Education:

GCSE, Lincoln College

September 2012 – June 2013

6 GCSEs grade C and above including English, Maths and Science

BTEC level 2, The Wolds college

September 2009 - June 2011

Multi skilled construction (Plastering, Tiling, P&D, Bricklaying, Roofing) Health and safety in the workplace

References: References are available on request.